John A. Lomax and Alan Lomax papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series VIII: Writings, 1907-1967
  - Our Singing Country by John A. Lomax (1941)
    - Research notes and transcripts (6 of 7) (Box-folder 14/451)
Sands, Col. A.L.P.
Saron, Alec
Savard, James M.
Schlecht, Eillism
Schriber, Thomas M.
Schumaker, Ethel Lomax
Schwartz, Josephine
Schwartz, Lavina S.
Schweiger, H. M.
Scott, Helen
Scott, Isabel R.
Seeger, Charles, 1886-1979
Seeger, Mike, 1933-2009
Seeger, Ruth Crawford, 1901-1953
Sessions, Kenosha
Seton, Charles B.
Shapiro, Elliott
Shattuck, Marquis E.
Shaub, Margret
Shawbitz, John
Shenton, W.S.
Shipley, R. B.
Simmons, Lee
Simpson, Dr. George
Simpson, George, E.
Sinclair, Luna
Smart, James R.
Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1905-1994
Smith, Edith Cook
Smith, Helena Huntington
Smith, Henry Nash
Smith, Hobart
Smith, Joseph F.
Smith, Moses
Smith, Nicol
Smith, R.R.
Smith, Ralph
Smith, Rebecca W.
Smith, Reed
Smith, Stephen W.
Sobol, Alfred
Somervell, Lt. Col. Brehon B.
Spalding, Col. I.
Spaziani, David
Spencer, Onah
Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977
Sprackling, Nelson
St. John, C. Wardell
Stammer, Peter
Starr, Roger
Stephens, Harry
Stevens, David H.
Stevens, S.K.
Stewart, E.B.
Stierhem, Eleanor
Stocker, Mildred
Stokes, Frederick A.
Stone, June E.
Stone, Mrs. Phil
Storm, Dan
Stoudt, John Baer
Stoutt, L.B.
Strauss, Harold
Strunk, W. Oliver (William Oliver), 1901-1980
Stryker, Elizabeth
Stryker, Florence Dean
Stryker, Mrs. Whitelaw
Strzilicki, Anthony
Studebaker, Gordon
Sturz, Elizabeth Lyttleton
Sulzer, Elmer G.
Sykes, James
Taggard, Ernestine
Tartt, Ruby Pickens
Taylor, Beal D.
Taylor, Davidson
Taylor, Paul S.
Thomas, Jean, 1881-1982
Thompson, Frank M.
Thompson, John
Thompson, Lincoln
Thompson, Mary S.
Thompson, Stith
Thomson, Charles A.
Torrent, Lewis, Paddy Miles, Bill Duchaine
Tucker, C.E.
Ulery, C.B.
Umble, John M.
Unger, Paul A.
Unger, Ross
Utay, Joseph
Van Waters, Vivian
Van Zant, Robert
Vance, John
Vann, William H.
Vass, M.L.
Vincent, Estenio
Vincent, John N.
Voegelin, Ermine W.
Wade, Florrie
Walfert, D.
Walker, John O.
Wallace, Mary Jo
Waller, Judith
Walters, Clay
Walton, Ivan
Walton, Ivan H.
Ward, Dora
Ward, Edward A.
Ward, H.H.
Waring, Jane
Waring, Jane Carolyn
Waterhouse, Helen
Waters, Clay
Waters, Edward N. (Edward Neighbor), 1906-1991
Watson, Frances
Weaver, H.R.
Webb, Ruth K.
Weeks, Edward, 1898-1989
Weeks, Raymond
Wellnew Motors
Wells, H.C.
Wells, Roxanna
Wendell, Barrett, 1855-1921
West, Anne Scott
Wetherald, Robert P.
Wheatley, Parker
Wheeler, Mary, 1892-1979
Whitaker, Helen
White, Clarence Cameron, 1880-1960
White, Joseph H.
Whitfield, Irene
Whitfield, Miss
Whitmire, Alice
Whitmore, Alice and Ross
Wiesner, Jerome B. (Jerome Bert), 1915-1994
Wilcock, Mollie
Wilcox, Mollie
Wilkin, Lucille
Williams, Clarence
Williams, John Fred
Wilson, Edings Whaley
Wilson, Rosa Warren
Winterbottham, J. M.
Witt, Edgar E.
Wolff, William
Wolley, Eddy
Wood, Elizabeth M.
Wood, Ray
Wright, Marjorie
Wright, Mrs. H. F.
Wyman, Loraine
Young, Kimball, 1893-1972
Zanzig, Augustus D. (Augustus Delafield)
Zwenig, Gertrude